tagline for my company [music] is
humanizing AI for care. We've talked
about how healthcare needs to be
emotionally ready before it can be
technologically ready. [music]
Help people feel safe, seen, and
empowered as that change happens.
latchment on something which is already
there and bend on that
>> and hundreds of thousands of dollars on
the data that powers the technology.
>> Wow, what an incredible moment. Um, yes.
So, Ktock, C A S E D O K, you can find
us at ktock.com.
>> Okay. And we solved uh and force
interoperability and we basically have
uh solved the acquisition of medical
records and the expense involved in the
acquisition of medical records. Look at
how we got to the hospital instead of
sort of at the hospital. Right now, the
antecedent is the story that we're
missing to solve a lot of the the issues
in healthcare that we face.
>> Well, I want to welcome everyone to the
signal room. Uh, this looks different
because we are in Las Vegas at Plant
Hollywood at the Put Data First
conference and I'm really really excited
about our next guest. We we've met over
the last 24 hours or so. um like to
welcome you Alita to the the Sigma Room
podcast. Uh it it's been fun so far, but
I'm most excited cuz you told me you
just launched your business. Um but
maybe we could talk just a little bit
just tell me a little bit about your
background and kind of talk about the
company and what your what your mission
is. Um but also want to kind of dig into
the juicy stuff that we're getting here
because this has been a fun event. I've
never been to an event where there's so
much excitement and passion.
welcome and let's let's hear about you.
>> Wow. Well, first of all, it's such an
honor to be here. Thank you so much for
having me on your show. I am so excited
to be here and I wouldn't miss if it's
for the world because clearly in the
midst of launch I I wanted to be here
because I couldn't miss an opportunity
because I know that Chris puts together
that that I get to meet the John Wake
survey and I don't know how else to say
it but it's u it's incredible and um and
as well as meeting you and I was so
thankful and um about me I've been aid
of mass torret and medical malpractice
parillegal for 35 years.
>> Oh, that sounds like AI.
>> Yeah, exactly. until you realize that um
you know I had to use a lot of uh tools
and uh learn how to program to be able
to manage the campaigns that I did at
the scale in rehears and you know uh I
had to learn quickly and in doing so I
definitely leverage AR in in a lot of
the uh you know processing and and rule
connections and things like that right
uh and you know my love for AI. I'm
still looking to uh potentially
integrating AI safely or to our just
launched product,
>> which leads us to the most important
thing is tell us about the product. What
is the name of your company? And by the
way, for you listeners, she really
wanted to be here because her company
actually launched officially yesterday
and she's here with us. Yeah.
>> Unbelievable.
>> Um wow, what an incredible moment. Um
yes. So Ktock, C A S E D O K, we can
find this at kstock.com.
And we solved uh at force
interoperability. And we basically have
uh solved the acquisition of medical
records and the expense will all been
the acquisition of medical records.
other and when I talk about medical
records I'm talking about the whole
corpus of medical records because
currently every patient portal only
reports a very small fraction of your ri
and we we needed to solve that because
at least from my perspective I know
health information is powerful and it
can mitigate malpractice and certainly
better inform our lives. So I set out to
solve the patients access and
transparency more than anything.
Absolute transparency in medical
records. If you're not seeing exactly
what your doctor sees, then come to case
because we can fix that. you are
composing a masterpiece for the ears of
the clinicians that are wanting to do
AI, but they're scared because chief
data officers like me really have not uh
done a good job of proactively listening
to where their pain points are. And
you're talking about one of the things I
hear most frequently is
interoperability.
Uh my friend Barry, I think you might
have met yesterday. We've been a
physician for a number of years and one
of his his beefs with us is that we talk
about interoperability but we really
haven't solved it yet and until we do
we're just continuing to keep people at
risk.
>> Absolutely. And then more importantly
when we talk about interoperability
currently anytime we see the word
interoperability they're really only
having a conversation about
interoperability of the core clinical
record. Our goal is to solve
interoperability for the entire corpus
of the medical lender. That's all
medical records, all images and all
itemized skills, right? And um you know
they come in different forms especially
because when you work with a hospital
and they can afford a very
tool at software versus you know a
practitioner in in a rural area may
still be working with paper. And so we
receive all of the information for the
patient record in native format. So if
it's in HL7, we receive an HL7. If it's
in PDF, we receive a media. And what we
are looking for is to collaborate in uh
in AI with uh in a way that's safe
because you can't necessarily put
privileged information absolutely can't
put privileged information into and and
know we're very interested in building a
pipelike to avail the entire cled record
history of a patient so that AI can be
unleashed on you know ending static
medicine. Look at how we got to the
hospital instead of what happened at the
hospital. You know, the antecedent is
the story that we're missing to solve a
lot of the the issues at health.
>> You you're you're talking about
something that I think is really really
important and you you refer to it as
people treating it as static.
We're we've been measuring performance
by the the picture of an average person
that no individual on earth actually
fits the profile. And we either penalize
or we incentivize a physician based on
how they care for their patient against
that profile.
It doesn't work from an economic
standpoint. It doesn't work from a
quality standpoint in terms of care. How
is it going to work if we treat AI with
the same approach? because they're still
calling it a practice of medicine which
means it's an ever evolving science and
we're always learning. If our
legislation and our policym
does not have that same approach we are
going to exacerbate a problem that's
already very very disruptive. So tell
me, you know, from your perspective, h
what are some of the things that you're
seeing and and how are you working to
address uh this evolution of it and
building the flexibility into what you
do because I mean there is change. I
mean I hope to god we don't ever have
another co but that was eye opening for
a lot of us because it was massively
disruptive and we had to adapt so fast
that we we did make some mistakes
>> right
>> unfortunately. How do we mitigate that?
And and how are you thinking about it?
Well, I I think that objective
information is uh art best cuz informing
the infor
um we have a duty to inform our
practitioners and you know they have a
duty to inform the pitches and but they
rely on
an accurate medical district and we are
all terrible historians of our health
and of our health history and you know
the fragmentation that we face today
is you know causing us if you want to do
the math um we've been paying for the
same
our entire lives is every time we go to
a doctor and we have to report him a
medical history of debt to fill out
another for high no
right and and if you think about the
cost of the encounter we pay for 15
minutes Okay. And those 15 minutes are
what we had to be be able to solve our
challenge. And uh five generally five of
those minutes can be assumed on trying
to relay it on history and and where
else you know they're coming up as
scribes to both char that relay. We hope
to solve it through this precision nexa
because we know that there's a complete
record. We activate the cocaine and you
want to you unleash AI safe to be able
to curate a precision medical history
and the oral history. So AI can help uh
not in adding to fragmentation or
hallucination cuz Jalan just produced an
article ethics in May of 2025
that showed the reliability their
emergency runs was 33%.
and the widow. That's a very
alarming rate to be relying on in those
instances. And so whereas we can at
least interject and inform um providers
on an emergency basis, a clear precise
medical history when the patient may not
be available to report it themselves can
save lives.
>> Right. Yeah, you you bring up a another
really interesting point because I don't
know what everyone else's experience is
like in their medical history, but I'm
old enough that there's a lot of things
I can't even remember. And if it's not
in the the record, how is a physician
going to be able to help me uh with with
an informed prognosis or our treatment?
>> And and we aren't we aren't um doctors.
We don't know if that has relevance or
clinical significance to the challenge
that we have today that would that might
you know might change you know their
their clinical plan. We don't know what
we don't know and and is it important,
right? I mean,
>> and isn't isn't it just time that we
unleash AI to ask to ask them those
questions?
>> I think you're right. I mean, and the
the challenge that we have to be mindful
of and the flexibility we have to have
um in our models has to account for the
fact that
things are still evolving.
And if you don't know what you don't
know, AI is not going to bridge that gap
for you completely. there's always going
to be the possibility that there's
missing information. And to me, that's
the most dangerous kind of bias because
you can't detect it because there's
nothing to detect,
>> right? And and interestingly enough,
healthcare is the only industry where we
have to pay to get the receipts for for
what we paid for. And you know that's
another problem that we we wanted to
solve because in accessibility in true
accessibility when you can look at your
complete record history in one place
I've never been able to do that in my
life and I'm and I'm the CEO of this
company right
>> I I haven't you know used it myself yet.
Currently we're only serving currently
enrolled members for United Healthcare
Etna and Florida Blue. We are
conditionally approved for
Medicare.gov's connected apps registry,
but we have to wait for the government
shutdown hopefully to end soon so that
we can be able to serve 65 million
Medicare enroles so that they could
scanning their uh license and health
card. They can uh access their medical
or complete medic Medicare record
history in one click.
you seem to have this go big or go home
approach because you're not starting
small. You you mentioned two of the
biggest insurance companies on the
planet. I
>> I didn't leave um a very successful
career as a parillegal. I can assure you
I have about a trillion dollars in
recovery. Um I have uh been privileged
in being able to work with titans of
law.
>> Amazing. and um educated by um you know
very uh amazing um geniuses in law and
you know being able to support what you
know they're advocating for gave me a
great sense of reward but I will share
that you know I left this career because
after 35 years in medical malpractice I
left um my um family member was involved
in an incident uh of medical malpractice
and I couldn't stop it even though it
was occurring and I knew it was
occurring as it was occurring and um so
I decided to leave my career and try to
mitigate this by better informing and
engaging patients so that they not only
access their entire medical record
history or claimed history that exists
in the carrier uh claim history. Um, but
you know, to own it, download it, keep
it, get every CT scan that appears
there, every MRI, whatever you paid,
whatever the insurance company paid for
that record. If it's $113,000 worth of
money, you're looking at $113,000 worth
of data that you're not that you don't
have. If I paid $113,000 for anything,
you can be sure I'd have that in the
safe.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> I'm just saying go get
>> while you can. Wow.
No, this is exciting and you know I wish
we could talk for like two more hours.
So I would love to have you back um if
you'd like this. I'm sure next time we
we have a conversation there's going to
be a lot more late breaking news because
what you're doing is so exciting and I I
know your your passion is going to get
results and I I am so grateful for you
to you're joining me today on on the
signal room and let's stay in touch. How
how do people reach reach you if they
want to want to get in touch with you?
Um, well, I'm on LinkedIn, of course.
Aleida Lanza, that's a l i da lanza. Um, my
website is or our website is kstock.com.
cas.com
and my email is ala ktock. Anybody who's
interested in bettering health, please
reach out and collaborate.
>> Yes. And if you're if you're trying to
figure out how to get excited about AI,
definitely follow up with this lady
because she's got passion and she's
excited. So, thanks again, El. It's been
a pleasure to have you on this show.
>> Thank you so much.
>> That's it for this episode of the Signal
Room. If today's conversation sparks
something in you, an idea, a challenge,
or a perspective worth amplifying, I'd
love to hear from you. Message me on
LinkedIn or visit signarroompodcast.com
to explore being a guest on an upcoming
episode. Until next time, stay tuned,
stay curious, and stay human.